Guide to the Murray Webb Latimer papers, 1930-1980 MS2082
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Papers, 1930-1980; MS2082 Series 1; 39.5 Linear feet
  - Sex Discrimination in Pension Plans, Includes City of Los Angeles vs. Manhart, undated (Box 77, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L594
  - National Health Insurance, undated (Box 77, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L600
  - Professional Association Pension Plans, undated (Box 77, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L602
  - T.W.A. Flight Engineers Retirement Plan, undated (Box 77, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L603
  - Steel Correspondence-Reports,Letters,and Lists of Things Sent to Pittsburgh, 1950 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L612
  - Insurance Contracts-Bethlehem Steel,U.S. Steel and Carnegie, undated (Box 77, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L621
  - Sickness and Hospitalization Rates.Blue Cross Hospitalization Coverage for Carnegie Illinois Steel Corporation, undated (Box 77, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L625
  - BUREAU OF OLD AGE AND SURVIVERS INSURANCE (B.O.A.S.I.) STEEL WAGE STUDY: -Data Memos, undated (Box 77, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L629
  - BUREAU OF OLD AGE AND SURVIVERS INSURANCE (B.O.A.S.I.) STEEL WAGE STUDY: -Data,Gradation Methods, undated (Box 77, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L629.A
  - BUREAU OF OLD AGE AND SURVIVERS INSURANCE (B.O.A.S.I.) STEEL WAGE STUDY: -Data, undated (Box 77, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L629.B
  - BUREAU OF OLD AGE AND SURVIVERS INSURANCE (B.O.A.S.I.) STEEL WAGE STUDY: -Data, undated (Box 77, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L629.C
  - BUREAU OF OLD AGE AND SURVIVERS INSURANCE (B.O.A.S.I.) STEEL WAGE STUDY: - Earnings,1% Sample, 1948-1951 (Box 77, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:L629.D
  - BUREAU OF OLD AGE AND SURVIVERS INSURANCE (B.O.A.S.I.) STEEL WAGE STUDY: -331 Workers,l% Sample, undated (Box 77, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system:L629.E
  - BUREAU OF OLD AGE AND SURVIVERS INSURANCE (B.O.A.S.I.) STEEL WAGE STUDY: -, Tabulations, Analysis of 331 Earnings, 1948-1952 (Box 77, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system:L629.F
  - BUREAU OF OLD AGE AND SURVIVERS INSURANCE (B.O.A.S.I.) STEEL WAGE STUDY: -Data, Superseded Tabulations, undated (Box 77, Folder 16)
    Original numbering system:L629.G
  - BUREAU OF OLD AGE AND SURVIVERS INSURANCE (B.O.A.S.I.) STEEL WAGE STUDY: -Corrections for 1952 Data, undated (Box 77, Folder 17)
    Original numbering system:L129.H
  - BUREAU OF OLD AGE AND SURVIVERS INSURANCE (B.O.A.S.I.) STEEL WAGE STUDY: -4 Q Workers, undated (Box 77, Folder 18)
    Original numbering system:L629.I
  - BUREAU OF OLD AGE AND SURVIVERS INSURANCE (B.O.A.S.I.) STEEL WAGE STUDY: Group Pension Rates-Metropolitan Life Insurance-Co:, Concerning Group Annuity Contract #1897, 1977-1978 (Box 77, Folder 19)
    Original numbering system:L651
  - Papers, undated (Box 78)
  - ALUMINUM INDUSTRIES INC.: -Perfect Circle Division, Dana Corp., 1964 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L679.A
  - ALUMINUM INDUSTRIES INC.: -Perfect Circle Division, Dana Corp., 1965-1966 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L679.B
  - ALUMINUM INDUSTRIES INC.: -Perfect Circle Division, Dana Corp., 1967 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L679.C
  - ALUMINUM COMPANY OF AMERICA: - Negotiations, 1959 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L685.A
  - ALUMINUM COMPANY OF AMERICA: -Guaranteed Annual Wage Study, undated (Box 78, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L685.B
  - ALUMINUM COMPANY OF AMERICA: -S.U.B.(;Suuplemental Unemployment Benefits), undated (Box 78, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L685.C
  - ALUMINUM COMPANY OF AMERICA: S.U.B., undated (Box 78, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L685.D
  - ALUMINUM COMPANY OF AMERICA: -ALCOA Products, undated (Box 78, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L685.E
  - ALUMINUM COMPANY OF AMERICA: -Insurance, undated (Box 78, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L685.F
  - ALUMINUM COMPANY OF AMERICA: -ALCOA Products Inc.,Closing, undated (Box 78, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L685.G
  - Papers, undated (Box 79)
  - CROWN CORM AND SEAL COMPANY, INC.: -Negotiations, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L731.A
  - CROWN CORM AND SEAL COMPANY, INC.: - Negotiations, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L731.B
  - CROWN CORM AND SEAL COMPANY, INC.: - Insurance Booklet, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L731.C
  - CROWN CORM AND SEAL COMPANY, INC.: -Crown Pension Funding, undated (Box 79, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L731.D
  - American Can, Negotiations, 1967 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L741
  - A.F.L. C.I.O.:-Staff Retirement Plan, 1970-1977 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L751
  - A.F.L. C.I.O.:-Industrial Union Department-Analysis;Otis Elevator Co., Whirlpool Corp.,White Consolidated Industries, undated (Box 79, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L752
  - Joseph Musher Memos-Miscl., undated (Box 79, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L759
  - Joseph Musher, Typed and Published Materials, 1960 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L761
  - Joseph Musher Material, not typed, undated (Box 79, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L762
  - National War Labor Board-Mediating Dispute Between United Steel Workers of America,C.I.O.,and 12 Non-integrated Steel Casting Companies, 1945 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L771
  - Tax Tables, D.C. and Federal, undated (Box 79, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L781
  - Staff Resumes (for Industrial Relations Counselers ?), undated (Box 79, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:L791
  - International Education Assembly-liason Committee and Proposals "Education For International Security", 1943 September (Box 79, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system:L811
  - University of California-Pension and Retirement Systems of the U. of Cal., 1954 (Box 79, Folder 16)
    Original numbering system:L831
  - Cleveland Management Clinic, 1950 May 16-1950 May 17 (Box 79, Folder 17)
    Original numbering system:L841
  - Columbia University Executive Program for Buisness Administration, 1953 June 23,August 27 (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Committee of Education and Labor Select Sub-committee on Labor,M.W.L. Statement, 1965 (Box 79, Folder 19)
    Original numbering system:L851
  - List of Companies,Industrial Pension System (M.W.L. Book) Index of Companies and Employment-valuation never completed, recalled census, undated (Box 79, Folder 20)
    Original numbering system:L861
  - List of Public Ut-lities-Reference to St. and Poors(?) for Change in Corporate Ownership, undated (Box 79, Folder 21)
    Original numbering system:L871
- Atomic Energy Commission, undated; MS2082 Series 2; 1 Linear feet
  This series contains correspondence, notes, contracts, and reports. Latimer was unofficially associated with this organization during his career.
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): -General, undated (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): -Federal Support Services, undated (Box 80, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L872
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): General Dynamics Corp,General Atomic Pension Plan, undated (Box 80, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system:L873
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): -Personal Notes,Miscl., undated (Box 80, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system:L874
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): -Miscl., undated (Box 80, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system:L875
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): -Hanford-Personal Notes, undated (Box 80, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system:L876
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): -Hanford-Computer Science Corporation, undated (Box 80, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:L877
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): -Hanford-Hanford Occupational Health Foundation, undated (Box 80, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:L878
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): -Hanford-Isochem,Inc., undated (Box 80, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system:L879
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): -Hanford-Deposit Administration Contract Proposal, undated (Box 80, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system:L881
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): -Hanford-Douglass Aircraft,Douglass United Nuclear Negotiations, undated (Box 80, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system:L882
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): -Hanford-Cost Reports, undated (Box 80, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system:L883
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): -Hanford-Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:L884
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): -Hanford-Correspondence, undated (Box 80, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system:L885
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): -Hanford-Hanford Enviromental Health Foundation Plan,Atlantic Richfield Hanford Co., undated (Box 80, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system:L866
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): -Hanford-Travelers,Proposals for Group Annuity, undated (Box 80, Folder 16)
    Original numbering system:L886.1
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): -San Francisco-Atomic International, North America Aviation, undated (Box 80, Folder 17)
    Original numbering system:L887
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): -Idaho Falls,Idaho Operations Concerning Electric, undated (Box 80, Folder 18)
    Original numbering system:L8888
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): -General Electric, undated (Box 80, Folder 19)
    Original numbering system:L889
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): -General Electric, undated (Box 80, Folder 20)
    Original numbering system:L891
  - Atomic Energy Commission, undated (Box 81)
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): -Pinellas Peninsula Operation, General Electric, undated (Box 81, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system:L892
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): -Schenectady Worksheet, undated (Box 81, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system:L893
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): -Lochland Office, Correspondence, Contract,G.E., undated (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): -Batelle Memorial Institute-Miscl. Applicable to WADCO, undated (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): -Batelle Memorial Institute-WADCO Data, 1970 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): -Batelle Memorial Institute-WADCO,Northwest, undated (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): -Westinghouse,Pittsburgh, undated (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): -VITRO Corporation of America, undated (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): -VITRO Corporation of America, undated (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION ( UN-NUMBERED): -Contracts, Miscl., undated (Box 81, Folder 10)
- Railroad Retirement Board, 1934-1947; MS2082 Series 3; 5 Linear feet
  This series contains correspondence, proposals, articles, inter-office memoranda, jurisdictional dockets, Congressional legislative records, and budgets. The material dates from 1934-47. This material concerns the Railroad Retirement Board for the years when Latimer was chair. The issues addressed are social insurance, maritime unemployment insurance, and retirement, and workmen's compensation.
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT LEGISLATION: -75th Congress, lst Session(1937) Preliminar Conferences-Correspondence, undated (Box 82, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system: 2
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT LEGISLATION: -75th Con ress,lst Session(1937) Preliminar Conferences-Drafts of Correspondence, undated (Box 82, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system: 4
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT LEGISLATION: -75th Congress, lst Session(1937) Preliminar Conferences-Proposed Plans, undated (Box 82, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system: 5
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT LEGISLATION: -75th Congress,lst Session(1937) Preliminar Conferences-Memoranda, undated (Box 82, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system: 10
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT LEGISLATION: -75th Congress, lst Session(1937) Preliminar Conferences-Drafts of Memoranda, undated (Box 82, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system: 12
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT LEGISLATION: -75th Congress, lst Session(1937) Preliminar Conferences-Drafts of Bills and Reports, undated (Box 82, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system: 25
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT LEGISLATION: -75th Congress,lst Session,Bills,Hearings,Reports and Congressional Record Clippings, undated (Box 82, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system:30
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT LEGISLATION: -75th Congress, 2nd and 3rd Sessions Bills,Hearings,Reports,and Congressional Record Clippings, undated (Box 82, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system:31
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT LEGISLATION: -76TH CONGRESS-1st Session, 1939, Bills, Hearinsgs, Reports and Congressionail Record clippings, undated (Box 82, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system: 32
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT LEGISLATION: -76TH CONGRESS-3rd Session, Bills, Reports, Hearings, and Cogressional Record Clippings, 1940 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system: 33
  - Railroad Retirement Board, undated (Box 83)
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT LEGISLATION: -76TH CONGRESS-76th Congress, 3rd Session,-Military Service Legislation. Bills, Reports an Congressional Record Clippings, 1940 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system: 33.1
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT LEGISLATION: -77th Congress-1st Session,1941.Bills,Hearings Reports,and Congressional Record Clippings, undated (Box 83, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system: 34
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT LEGISLATION: -77th Congress-1st Session,1941.Military Service Legislation, undated (Box 83, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system: 34.1
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT LEGISLATION: -77th Congress-2nd Session, 1942. Bills, Hearings,and Reports, undated (Box 83, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system: 35
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT LEGISLATION: -77th Congress-2nd Session.Military Service Legislation, undated (Box 83, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system: 35.1
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT LEGISLATION: -78th Congress-1st Session, 1943.Bills,Hearings,and Reports, undated (Box 83, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system: 36
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT LEGISLATION: -78th Congress-1st Session,Extra and Draft Copies, undated (Box 83, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system: 36.1
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT LEGISLATION: -78th Congress-2nd Session.Bills,Reports,and Debates, undated (Box 83, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system: 36.2
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT LEGISLATION: -78th Congress-2nd Session.Correspondence and Memoranda, undated (Box 83, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system: 36.3
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT LEGISLATION: -78th Congress-2nd Session,1944. Military Service Legislation, Memoranda, undated (Box 83, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system: 36.5
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT LEGISLATION: -79th Congress, lst Session,1945, Bills and Reports, undated (Box 83, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system: 37
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT LEGISLATION: -Acts and Amendments, Miscl., undated (Box 83, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system: 38
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT LEGISLATION: -Bills and Comments, undated (Box 83, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system: 39
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT LEGISLATION: -Monthly Comparison Under Railroad Act with Crosser and Wolverton Bills, undated (Box 83, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system: 39.1
  - Railroad Retirement Board, undated (Box 84)
  - UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE LEGISLATION-75th Congress: - Correspondence, 1938 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system: 50
  - UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE LEGISLATION-75th Congress: -Memoranda and Drafts, 1937-1938 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system: 51
  - UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE LEGISLATION-75th Congress: -Memoranda, 1937 March-1938 April (Box 84, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system: 51.1
  - UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE LEGISLATION-75th Congress: -lst Session, Memoranda, 1938 May-June (Box 84, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system: 51.2
  - UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE LEGISLATION-75th Congress: -Drafts and Memoranda, undated (Box 84, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system: 52
  - UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE LEGISLATION-75th Congress: --Cost Memoranda, 1937-1938 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system: 55
  - UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE LEGISLATION-75th Congress: -Mimeographed Copies of Memoranda, undated (Box 84, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system: 60
  - UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE LEGISLATION-75th Congress: -,Type Written Drafts'of Bills, 1937-1938 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system: 68
  - UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE LEGISLATION-75th Congress: -Mimeographed Copies of Bills, 1937 August 02-1938 March 26 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system: 69
  - UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE LEGISLATION-75th Congress: -3rd Session,1938,Bills,Reports,and Congressional Recod Clipping (Box 84, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system: 71
  - UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE LEGISLATION-75th Congress: -3rd Session,1938, Bills,Reports, and Congressional Record Clippings (Box 84, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system: 75
  - Railroad Retirement Board, undated (Box 85)
  - UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE LEGISLATION: -76th Congress-1st Session,.Proposed Amendments to Railroad Unemployment Insurance Act(R.U.I.A.), 1939 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system: 76
  - UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE LEGISLATION: -76th Congress-3rd Session, Proposed Amendments to R.U.I.A.-Miscl. Papers, 1940 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system: 77
  - UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE LEGISLATION: -76th Congress-3rd Session,.Reports and Other Data on House Bills, 1940 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system: 77.1
  - UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE LEGISLATION: -76th Congress-3rd Session,. Reports and Other Data no Senate Bills, 1940 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system: 77.2
  - UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE LEGISLATION: -76th Congress-3rd Session,.Transfer Funds From Kentucky to Railroad Unemployment Insurance Account (R.U.I.), 1940 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system: 77.3
  - UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE LEGISLATION: -76th Congress-3rd Session,. Extra and Draft Copies of Material in File, 1940 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system: 77.5
  - UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE LEGISLATION: -77th Congress-1st and 2nd Sessions,; Proposed Amendments to R.U.I.A., 1941-1942 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system: 78
  - UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE LEGISLATION: -77th Congress-2nd Session,Proposed Amendment H.R. 7534-Elliot Bill,Correspondence Memoranda,Reports,and Related Material, undated (Box 85, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system: 78.1
  - UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE LEGISLATION: -78th Congress-1st and 2nd Sessions-Proposed Amendments to R.U.I.A., undated (Box 85, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system: 79
  - UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE LEGISLATION: -78th Congress-1st and 2nd Sessions, Transfer Funds From Kentucky yo R.U.I. Account, 1943 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system: 79.3
  - UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE LEGISLATION: -78th Congress-2nd Session,G.I. Bill, Reports,Memoranda,and Correspondence, undated (Box 85, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system: 80
  - UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE LEGISLATION: -78th Congress-2nd Session, Reconversion Legislation, Kilgor Bill George Bill, act. Related Material, undated (Box 85, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system: 81
  - UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE LEGISLATION: -79th Congress-1st Session,R.U.I.A.-Bills and Reports, undated (Box 85, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system:82
  - UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE LEGISLATION: -79th Congress-Transfer of Funds from Kentucky-Reports, Correspondence, Memoranda, undated (Box 85, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system: 82.3
  - Railroad Retirement Board, undated (Box 86)
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT BOARD: -Announcements and Circular Letters Originated by Railroad Retirement Board Members and Secretary, 1937-1940 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    Original numbering system: 100
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT BOARD: -Announcements and Circular Letters Originated by Railroad Retirement Board Members and Secretary, 1941 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    Original numbering system: 100.1
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT BOARD: -Actuarial Material, undated (Box 86, Folder 3)
    Original numbering system: 101
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT BOARD: -Disabled Lives; Superseded Materials, undated (Box 86, Folder 4)
    Original numbering system: 101.a
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT BOARD: -Board Minutes of Meeting, 1967 May 23 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    Original numbering system: 101.b
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT BOARD: -Extra Copies of Railroad Retirement Act, Railroad Unemployment Insurance Act, Interstate Commerce Act,CTA and Booklets, undated (Box 86, Folder 6)
    Original numbering system: 106
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT BOARD: -Administrative Speeches, Copies, Drafts, and Correspondence, 1937-1939 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    Original numbering system: 115
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT BOARD: -Administrative Speeches, Copies, Drafts, and Correspondence, 1940 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    Original numbering system: 115.1
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT BOARD: -Newspaper and Magazine Clippings, undated (Box 86, Folder 9)
    Original numbering system: 116
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT BOARD: -Civil Service Commission, Correspondence and Department Circulars, undated (Box 86, Folder 10)
    Original numbering system: 117
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT BOARD: -Federal Administrative Procedure Legislation Bills, Correspondence, Memoranda, undated (Box 86, Folder 11)
    Original numbering system: 117.5
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT BOARD: -RRA & RUIA-Coverage of Mexican Nationals, Correspondence and Memoranda, undated (Box 86, Folder 12)
    Original numbering system: 141
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT BOARD: -Building Projects, RR Retirement Bd., 1941 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    Original numbering system: 145.1
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT BOARD: -Miscl. Memoranda, undated (Box 86, Folder 14)
    Original numbering system: 148.1
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT BOARD: -Interoffice. Memoranda, Rose Pualson, Martha S. Gorman, 1942-1943 (Box 86, Folder 15)
    Original numbering system: 148.la
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT BOARD: -Interoffice Memoranda, 1944-1946 (Box 86, Folder 16)
    Original numbering system: 148.lb
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT BOARD: -Mr. J.G. Luhrsen s Office, Correspondence and Memoranda, undated (Box 86, Folder 17)
    Original numbering system: 162.1
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT BOARD: -Mr. F.C. Squire's Office, Correspondence and Memoranda, undated (Box 86, Folder 18)
    Original numbering system: 164.1
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT BOARD: -Comparisons of Benefits Under RR Retirement Act and Social Security Act Memoranda, undated (Box 86, Folder 19)
    Original numbering system: 169
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT BOARD: -Actuarial Advisory Committee; Reports, Memoranda, Correspondence, undated (Box 86, Folder 20)
    Original numbering system: 191
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT BOARD: -RR Retirement Board Seminar in Management, and Glossary, 1939-1940 (Box 86, Folder 21)
    Original numbering system: 198
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT BOARD: -Bureau of Administration, Division of Finance, Budget,: Estimates for Bureau of the Budget, 1945 (Box 86, Folder 22)
    Original numbering system: 209.6
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT BOARD: -Finance, Budget,1846, Estimates for The Bureau of the Budget. Treasury Department Correspondence; Appropriation Legislation, undated (Box 86, Folder 23)
    Original numbering system: 209.8
  - RAILROAD RETIREMENT BOARD: -Budget Estimates act., 1947 (Box 86, Folder 24)
    Original numbering system: 209.10
  - Railroad Retirement Board, undated (Box 87)